[
  {
    "question": "1 x 4",
    "options": ["1", "4", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 4",
    "options": ["4", "8", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 4",
    "options": ["3", "7", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 4",
    "options": ["16", "20", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 4",
    "options": ["20", "25", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 4",
    "options": ["24", "28", "32"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 4",
    "options": ["28", "30", "35"],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 4",
    "options": ["30", "32", "36"],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 4",
    "options": ["34", "36", "40"],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 4",
    "options": ["36", "40", "44"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  }
]
